这就是我杀死猛龙的全过程
Web... and that's how I slay the dragon.
嘿  亚蒂  你有空么
Hey, Artie, you got a minute?
你好啊  乔伊
Hey, Joey.
你有女朋友啦
You got a girlfriend?
好啊
Burn!
这怎么会好啊  去年秋天你把你妈带到新生舞会上去了
How is that a burn? You took your mom to the freshman dance last fall.
那是什么风把你吹回了
So, what brings you crawling back
学校的太  太  太
to the Society of Space... Space... space...
空  空  空
Were... were... were... Wol... wol... wol...
狼  狼  狼  人  人  社团
wol... wol... wol... ves... ves?
我被投票开除了社团籍
I was voted out of the Society
只是因为觉得戴个狼尾巴很蠢
for suggesting that wolf tails were stupid.
我错了吗
Was I wrong?
同志们  我哪里错了
People, was I wrong?
我想跟你谈谈我姐丽芙的事
I want to talk to you about my sister Liv.
别  啦啦啦我听不见
No la la la la.
我们绝不会说出那个想亵渎特里斯坦的
We do not speak the name of that she-devil
女魔头的名字
who wants to desecrate Tristan.
除非她委托你来请我陪她跳舞
Unless she sent you to ask me to prom,
这样的话  跟她说我也许会答应
in which case, let her know I say maybe.
不见不散了
Be gone with you.
听好了  亚蒂
Listen, Artie.
我们有个公敌啊
We have a common enemy here,
我们必须通力合作
and we need to work together
来保证特里斯坦的神圣地位
to defend the iconic character
不可被撼动
that is Tristan.
你我原本是强有力的同盟
We were once powerful allies, you and I.
磕碰不断的盟友啊
An uneasy alliance.
我的狼耳朵竖起来了
My wolf ears are perked.
丽芙明天会到纳维尔商店
Liv will be down at Neville's tomorrow.
我要让你给她秀秀《太空狼人》
I need you to show her the real fangs
脑残粉真正的獠牙
of a true "Space Werewolves" fanboy.
脑残粉
Fanboy?
这可是个贬义词啊  同志
That term is derogatory, sir.
我们更喜欢被称作“空想主义爱好者”
We prefer "fantasy enthusiast."
所以你要去砸场子
So will you do it?
哦  听起来爽极了  乔伊
Oh, sounds great, Joey.
我会高兴地跳着舞钻进你的圈套里啊
I'd happily waltz right into your trap.
你把我当傻瓜了吗
Do you take me for a fool?!
是的  我确实把你当傻瓜了
Yes. Yes, I do.
而换做特里斯坦的话就是
But as Tristan himself would say...
当你的敌人
When an enemy
伸出了魔爪  舔一口吧
offers his  paw, lick it.
若你可在明日将他的后腿
If only to tear off his hind leg...
碎成万段
Tomorrow.
哦
Oh!
不去踢馆子就像是
Saying no to that would be like
背叛了特里斯坦一样
saying no to Tristan himself.
干得漂亮  孤狼
Well played, lone wolf.
干得够漂亮
Well played indeed.
啊
Aah!
傻缺
Nerds!